[
  {
    "id": "rel_001",
    "text": "Tim Cook has been the CEO of Apple since 2011.",
    "subject": "Tim Cook",
    "object": "Apple",
    "subject_type": "PERSON",
    "object_type": "ORGANIZATION",
    "display": "**Text:** Tim Cook has been the CEO of Apple since 2011.\n\n**Subject:** [Tim Cook] (PERSON)\n**Object:** [Apple] (ORGANIZATION)"
  },
  {
    "id": "rel_002",
    "text": "The Eiffel Tower is located in Paris, France.",
    "subject": "Eiffel Tower",
    "object": "Paris",
    "subject_type": "LOCATION",
    "object_type": "LOCATION",
    "display": "**Text:** The Eiffel Tower is located in Paris, France.\n\n**Subject:** [Eiffel Tower] (LOCATION)\n**Object:** [Paris] (LOCATION)"
  },
  {
    "id": "rel_003",
    "text": "Jeff Bezos founded Amazon in his garage in 1994.",
    "subject": "Amazon",
    "object": "Jeff Bezos",
    "subject_type": "ORGANIZATION",
    "object_type": "PERSON",
    "display": "**Text:** Jeff Bezos founded Amazon in his garage in 1994.\n\n**Subject:** [Amazon] (ORGANIZATION)\n**Object:** [Jeff Bezos] (PERSON)"
  },
  {
    "id": "rel_004",
    "text": "Marie Curie was born in Warsaw and later moved to France.",
    "subject": "Marie Curie",
    "object": "Warsaw",
    "subject_type": "PERSON",
    "object_type": "LOCATION",
    "display": "**Text:** Marie Curie was born in Warsaw and later moved to France.\n\n**Subject:** [Marie Curie] (PERSON)\n**Object:** [Warsaw] (LOCATION)"
  }
]
