[
  {
    "id": "mtacred_001",
    "text": "John Smith, a senior engineer at Microsoft, has been working at the company's headquarters in Redmond since 2015.",
    "language": "en",
    "subject": "John Smith",
    "subject_type": "PERSON",
    "object": "Microsoft",
    "object_type": "ORGANIZATION"
  },
  {
    "id": "mtacred_002",
    "text": "Angela Merkel wurde 1954 in Hamburg geboren und wuchs in Templin in der DDR auf.",
    "language": "de",
    "subject": "Angela Merkel",
    "subject_type": "PERSON",
    "object": "Hamburg",
    "object_type": "CITY"
  },
  {
    "id": "mtacred_003",
    "text": "La empresa Tesla fue fundada por Elon Musk en 2003 y tiene su sede central en Austin, Texas.",
    "language": "es",
    "subject": "Tesla",
    "subject_type": "ORGANIZATION",
    "object": "Elon Musk",
    "object_type": "PERSON"
  },
  {
    "id": "mtacred_004",
    "text": "Le président Emmanuel Macron, diplômé de l'ENA, a été élu à l'âge de 39 ans en 2017.",
    "language": "fr",
    "subject": "Emmanuel Macron",
    "subject_type": "PERSON",
    "object": "ENA",
    "object_type": "ORGANIZATION"
  },
  {
    "id": "mtacred_005",
    "text": "Samsung Electronics, headquartered in Suwon, South Korea, is a subsidiary of Samsung Group.",
    "language": "en",
    "subject": "Samsung Electronics",
    "subject_type": "ORGANIZATION",
    "object": "Samsung Group",
    "object_type": "ORGANIZATION"
  },
  {
    "id": "mtacred_006",
    "text": "Fizyikçi Stephen Hawking, 1942'de Oxford'da doğmuş ve 2018'de Cambridge'de hayatını kaybetmiştir.",
    "language": "tr",
    "subject": "Stephen Hawking",
    "subject_type": "PERSON",
    "object": "Oxford",
    "object_type": "CITY"
  },
  {
    "id": "mtacred_007",
    "text": "Papież Jan Paweł II, urodzony jako Karol Wojtyła w Wadowicach w Polsce, był głową Kościoła katolickiego od 1978 roku.",
    "language": "pl",
    "subject": "Jan Paweł II",
    "subject_type": "PERSON",
    "object": "Wadowicach",
    "object_type": "CITY"
  },
  {
    "id": "mtacred_008",
    "text": "Alibaba Group was founded by Jack Ma in Hangzhou in 1999 and has since expanded to become one of the world's largest e-commerce companies.",
    "language": "en",
    "subject": "Alibaba Group",
    "subject_type": "ORGANIZATION",
    "object": "Jack Ma",
    "object_type": "PERSON"
  },
  {
    "id": "mtacred_009",
    "text": "Компания Яндекс была основана Аркадием Воложем в 2000 году и базируется в Москве.",
    "language": "ru",
    "subject": "Яндекс",
    "subject_type": "ORGANIZATION",
    "object": "Москве",
    "object_type": "CITY"
  },
  {
    "id": "mtacred_010",
    "text": "Nokia Oyj, originally founded in 1865 in Tampere, Finland, served as the world's largest mobile phone manufacturer from 1998 to 2012.",
    "language": "en",
    "subject": "Nokia Oyj",
    "subject_type": "ORGANIZATION",
    "object": "Tampere",
    "object_type": "CITY"
  }
]
